http://www.cardplayer.com/privacy

Sign In
/
Register
Poker Coverage:
Privacy Policy
Thank you for reviewing our Privacy Policy. Your online safety is of utmost importance to us.
This is Card Player Media, LLC's Privacy Policy, which is effective as of March 7, 2008, and describes how Card Player collects and uses information from the Card Player Card Player website and subscriber information. Card Player respects the privacy rights of our users and recognizes the importance of protecting the information collected about you. Card Player uses your data to administer your subscription, provide information of interest to you, and to communicate with you. Card Player stores your data in the United States, and our use of your data is subject to this privacy policy. This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on this page. If we make a significant or material change in the way we use your personal information, the change will be posted on this page thirty (30) days prior to taking effect and registered users will be notified via e-mail. If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy, or wish to contact us, please send an email to
support@cardplayer.com.
Types of Information Collected
Personally Identifiable Information
Personal information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you on-line or off-line. Card Player collects personal information from our online visitors during account registration, or through sign-ups for newsletter and magazine subscriptions, referral services, and other marketing surveys and email campaigns.
Information collected will vary depending upon the activity and may include your name, e-mail address, phone number, home address, birth date, and credit card information. In addition, we may collect demographic information such as gender, zip code, software, platform, Internet IP address and connection, information about your use of the website such as click paths and other data that you may provide in surveys or online profiles. We may combine demographic information with personal information, such as email address, to tailor our offerings or web pages to your preferences or interests.
Aggregate Information
We may store non-personally identifiable information that we collect through log files to create a profile of our users in the aggregate. Log files record internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks which we will use to analyze trends, administer the Service or Card Player website, track aggregate service and usage patterns, and gather broad demographic information for general use. Your individual usage cannot be tracked through aggregate data.
As is standard practice on many web sites, Card Player may use "cookies" and other technologies to recognize you and provide personalization, as well as to help us understand which parts of our web site is the most popular, where our visitors are going and how much time they spend there.
Online Chat Rooms and Profiles
You may choose to disclose information, including personal information, about yourself through chat functions, message boards, screen name profiles for public view, or in similar forums on the website. Information that you disclose through these features is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality there. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of those features, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit through these features.
Children
When creating an account, we require the new member to certify that he or she is 18 years old or over by checking the appropriate box. If a child under age 18 attempts to register with CardPlayer.com, we ask that he or she have a parent or guardian create a CardPlayer.com Family Account to obtain parental permission.
CardPlayer.com will not contact children under age 18 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission.
CardPlayer.com does not ask a child under age 18 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity or promotion.
How We Use the Information
Account Maintenance and Transactions
We use your personal information to maintain your Card Player account and subscription and to provide the website to you. In addition, the personal information you provide will allow us to alert you to new products, features and enhancements; special offers; upgrade opportunities; and events of interest. We may send you electronic communications about Card Player products or services.
Statistical Analysis
Card Player may perform statistical, demographic and marketing analyses of users, and their usage patterns, for product development purposes and to generally inform advertisers about the nature of our user base.
Products and Services from Third Parties
From time to time, Card Player may share your personal information with companies and organizations that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We see this as a value-added service helping you to find useful products or services. We strive to limit use of the information you provide to those offers that we think you would appreciate receiving. You may opt-out of receiving these offers by calling Card Player at 1-866-587-6537.To opt out of further communications from a marketing partner or sponsor with whom your information has been shared while you had opted-in to receiving such communications, please contact that partner directly.
Changing or Updating Your Information
You can correct or update your account information at any time by calling Card Player at 1-866-587-6537. We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. We may still retain your information in our files however, to resolve disputes, enforce our terms of use, and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of the Service and our websites.
Card Player also sends regular newsletter updates to registered members. To opt out of these communications, access the Unsubscribe page and enter your email address. Then select the communications you choose to opt out of, and hit submit.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number numbers) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact support@cardplayer.com.
COPPA Compliance
Card Player does not knowingly collect or store any personal information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of 13.
Compliance with Legal Process
We may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to: (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our web sites; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).
Third-Party Web Beacons:
We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!,
click here
Questions and Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at
support@cardplayer.com.
POPULAR PAGES
Poker News
Poker Videos
Poker Players
Poker Leaderboards
Poker Blogs
Poker Twitter
Nevada
ABOUT CARDPLAYER, THE POKER AUTHORITY
CardPlayer.com is the world's oldest and most well respected poker magazine and online poker guide. Since 1988,
CardPlayer has provided poker players with poker strategy, poker news, and poker results.
Today, CardPlayer.com
is the best poker information portal for free poker content, offering online poker site reviews and exclusive online
poker bonus deals.
We offer daily poker news, poker professionals' blogs and tweets, exclusive poker videos, thousands of free poker
articles, as well as coverage from all major poker tournaments in the world.
You can also find here poker player
profiles, tournament poker results, poker rules, poker strategy articles, poker magazines, poker tools
and poker training resources.
Ever wonder who is the best poker player in the world? Check out our Poker Player of the Year race, as well as years of data of poker player results and casino poker tournament pay-outs.
WWW.CARDPLAYER.COM
Home
About Us
Advertise With Us
Newsletter Sign Up
Subscription Support
Terms of Use
Disclaimer
Copyright © 2001-2020 CardPlayer.com. All rights reserved.
